<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="First steps with Foglyn">
  <intro>
    <description>This tutorial will help you start using Foglyn. You will specify your FogBugz server and setup Foglyn to use your cases.</description>
  </intro>
  <item title="Open the Task Repositories view">
    <description>
      First step in using Foglyn is configuring so-called <b>Task Repository</b>. Task repository is a source of tasks, like FogBugz cases.<br/><br/>

 To add your FogBugz server as a task repository, you need to open <b>Task Repositories</b> view first.<br/><br/>
 
 Select <b>Window &gt; Show View &gt; Other</b> in the menu at the top of the workbench and choose <b>Mylyn &gt; Task Repositories</b> view from list of views.
    </description>
    <command
          required="false"
          serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=org.eclipse.mylyn.tasks.ui.views.repositories)"/>
  </item>

  <item title="Create FogBugz repository" dialog="true">
    <description>
      Now you will configure access to your FogBugz server.
<br/><br/>

In <b>Task Repositories</b> view select <b>Add Task Repository</b> button from the toolbar.<br/><br/>

In <b>Add Task Repository</b> dialog, select <b>FogBugz repository (Foglyn plugin)</b> and choose <b>Next</b> button.
<br/><br/>

In the next page, you need to enter details about your FogBugz server.<br/><br/>

<b>Server:</b> location of server, for example http://ondemand.fogbugz.com/<br/>
<b>Label:</b> custom name of server, for example &quot;My FogBugz Server&quot;.<br/>
<b>User ID:</b> your full name or email address, as known to FogBugz.<br/>
<b>Password:</b> your FogBugz password.
<br/><br/>

After you enter all these values, use <b>Validate Settings</b> button to check if Foglyn can connect to your server.
<br/><br/>
When you are done, select <b>Finish</b> button.
    </description>
    <command
          required="false"
          serialization="org.eclipse.mylyn.tasks.ui.command.addTaskRepository(connectorKind=foglyn)"/>
  </item>

  <item title="Create new query" dialog="true">
    <description>
       To work with your cases, you need to specify which cases should Foglyn present to you by creating a <b>query</b>.
<br/><br/>   
To create a query, go to <b>Task Repositories</b> view again, and select your new FogBugz repository you created in previous step. From context menu choose <b>New Query...</b> item.
<br/><br/>
In this dialog you can choose to create query from preexisting options (My Cases, My Cases for Project, My Cases for Milestone), query based on filter or using advanced search options. Select <b>My Cases</b> for now and click <b>Finish</b> button.
    </description>
    <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.eclipse.mylyn.tasks.ui.wizards.new.query)" confirm="true" />
  </item>

  <item title="View your cases">
    <description>
      Your cases are visible in <b>Task List</b> view. To open this view, select <b>Window &gt; Show View &gt; Other</b> in the menu at the top of the workbench. In <b>Show View</b> dialog choose <b>Mylyn &gt; Task List</b> view from list of views.
    </description>
    <command
          required="false"
          serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=org.eclipse.mylyn.tasks.ui.views.tasks)"/>
  </item>
  <item
        title="Congratulations!">
     <description>
        You have successfully completed this tutorial. You have added your FogBugz server and you can now see your FogBugz cases in <b>Task List</b> view. From here you can open your cases and start working with them.
     </description>
  </item>
</cheatsheet>
